Roy Justus Papers
Roy Justus Papers
- Artwork
  - By Justus
    - 1969 Jan-Jun (Oversize 46)
      Jan 10: Just proves how clever we are!
      Jan 13: What they're trying to say is peace!
      Jan 14: That looks like a big pie to me!
      Jan 15: The new driver
      Jan 16: The legacy!
      Jan 17: At last. They've got a table!
      Jan 20: (no caption)
      Jan 21: That nag's gentle at first...
      Jan 22: And he sent forth a dove
      Jan 23: Mind if I watch?
      Jan 24: The medium is the message!
      Jan 27: Middle east badminton
      Jan 28: The table is o.k. - now it's a question of chairs!
      Jan 29: The calm before the storm
      Jan 30: Mythland
      Jan 31: Consolation prize
      Feb 3: Think!
      Feb 4: Snow, snow - beautiful snow!
      Feb 5: Awkward posture
      Feb 6: I pronounce you innocent...
      Feb 7: The doctor is in consultation
      Feb 11: Double trouble
      Feb 12: Sorry about this, kids!
      Feb 13: The new chief (U.S. world cop, Nixon
      Feb 14: Grim recorder
      Feb 17: Thanks, doc!
      Feb 18: At last - one world
      Feb 19: Now who did all this?
      Feb 20: Will this be our heritage?
      Feb 21: You'll never be a success until you become more aggressive!
      Feb 24: Suggested peaceful use of atomic bomb
      Feb 25: This will scare hell out 0' the commies!
      Feb 26: Another leaning tower
      Feb 27: Have patience over there - I've got him treed!
      Feb 28: Uncle Sam should blush
      Mar 3: Triumphant return from Europe
      Mar 4: Now what. Do you think you're doing?
      Mar 5: Where even angels fear to tread
      Mar 6: How'd you ever get in here?
      Mar 7: Signs of life again
      Mar 10: The vanguard (hunger, violence)
      Mar 11: Don't be alarmed: he's your protector!
      Mar 12: Say, Hubert - are you still interested in this job?
      Mar 13: (no caption)
      Mar 14: By golly - it's real!
      Mar 17: A foot in the door
      Mar 18: Most amazing feat of modern times
      Mar 19: Does it seem like the road's getting rougher, Spiro?
      Mar 20: (no caption)
      Mar 21: Just another mirage!
      Mar 24: I'm miserable!
      Mar 25: The arms race goes on - and on!
      Mar 26: The glutton
      Mar 27: It's going to take a long time to get out of this!
      Mar 28: Flood season
      Mar 31: He serves me most who serves his country best
      Apr 1: Senate doves
      Apr 2: Watchdog
      Apr 3: The thin shield
      Apr 4: Springtime
      Apr 7: Bulletin: we are now making progress (U.S., Vietnam)
      Apr 8: Limited vocabulary
      Apr 10: Not enough boys at the dike!
      Apr 11: How much is too much?
      Apr 14: Fat cat
      Apr 15: About this time of year
      Apr 16: The overweight problem
      Apr 17: Here we go again
      Apr 18: Must be a nightmare (Nixon's war)
      Apr 21: Always the dominant figure
      Apr 22: The open society
      Apr 23: Nixon: you mean you like it?
      Apr 24: How times have changed
      Apr 25: I think I saw a foot move!
      Apr 28: We're waiting for this demonstration!
      Apr 29: The inevitable retreat
      Apr 30: Atlas dropped the ball!
      May 1: Best-kept secret
      May 2: The juggernaut
      May 5: And now on the home front!
      May 6: (no caption)
      May 7: Violence vise
      May 8: Where is the offense department?
      May 9: I'm afraid I'm losing my popularity (war)
      May 27: You've flunked!
      May 28: But, Dick - isn't that subversive?
      May 29: Remember those good old 'pre-generation gap' days?
      May 30: Dangerous side effects
      Jun 3: Might change your disposition, too!
      Jun 4: What kind of teamwork is this?
      Jun 5: Naturally!
      Jun 6: Strengthening our ties!
      Jun 9: Now, now - after all, it's how you played the game!
      Jun 10: Mind blowers
      Jun 11: The elusive phrase
      Jun 12: Spawning ground
      Jun 13: He's gaining on you, dick!
      Jun 16: Let's do it in a more friendly spirit!
      Jun 17: The cliffhanger
      Jun 18: My dear friend, have no fear - I will protect you (U.S. military, dictator Franco, Spanish freedom)
      Jun 19: I want good simple solutions to complicated problems - but quick!
      Jun 20: Prince and pauper
      Jun 23: Great American debate
      Jun 24: Earl warren was here
      Jun 25: ABM intelligence credibility gap
      Jun 26: Return of the crusader (U.S.)
      Jun 27: Heh, heh - now what'll I do with it?
    - 1969 Jul-Dec (Oversize 47)
      Jul 1: What're you griping about - I didn't make any campaign promises, did I?
      Jul 2: Perpetual motion
      Jul 3: Wait 'til that stuff wears off!
      Jul 4: The wanderer
      Jul 7: I wouldn't withdraw too rapidly, Mr. President!
      Jul 8: But I wouldn't want to live there (Rockefeller, fact-finding mission to Latin America)
      Jul 9: Whipsaw
      Jul 10: The middle east dialogue
      Jul 14: The warmonger
      Jul 15: Broke his pick (Vietnam, U.S. foreign policy)
      Jul 17: Symbolic stride
      Jul 18: Money isn't the only ingredient
      Jul 21: The egg
      Jul 22: Moonlight
      Jul 23: Back in the limelight,
      Jul 24: Point of diminishing returns
      Jul 25: My, my - how well you look!
      Jul 28: The stray
      Aug 26: Grab bag (military, foreign economic aid, critical domestic needs, federal budget)
      Aug 27: When you can defend yourself we'll withdraw our troops!
      Aug 28: Did he say dangerous?
      Aug 29: Ah've said many 'times ah'm waitin' for the other side to reciprocate!
      Sep 1: The die-hards
      Sep 2: Adult education
      Sep 3: Go 'way - there won't be any crumbs!
      Sep 4: Still trying to allure the dove
      Sep 5: (no caption)
      Sep 8: All I need is a nice, snappy slogan!
      Sep 9: More pollution
      Sep 11: Where the action is
      Sep 12: Democracy is still breathing-he just fainted fr011 fright!
      Sep 12: No quibbling here
      Sep 15: Oh what a tangled web we've woven!
      Sep 16: Nixon's war
      Sep 17: Boy - what a relief!
      Sep 18: Self-determination in south Vietnam
      Sep 24: One of these days we ought to do something about this!
      Sep 25: Lost key
      Sep 26: Poor nasty, sinful, wretched me!
      Sep 29: You ain't got a thing to worry about!
      Sep 30: Now folks, I'll tell ya what I'm gonna do (Vietnamization snake oil, bring the boys home by Xmas, Nixon)
      Oct 1: The new Uncle Sam?
      Oct 2: Backlash!
      Oct 3: Gold rush prospects?
      Oct 6: One cease-fire he favors
      Oct 7: Now you too?
      Oct 8: Hell, no - I won't go!
      Oct 9: Disposal
      Oct 10: By golly - it works!
      Oct 13: Feeding the stork
      Oct 14: Gloomy prospects
      Oct 15: The split is becoming more evident
      Oct 16: Shades of Joe McCarthy!
      Oct 20: Now what wise guy did that?
      Oct 21: Gosh! - did I do that?
      Oct 22: What's gotten into this old nag?!
      Oct 23: Generation gap
      Oct 24: But Spiro, can't you find a little smaller brush? (Agnew, GOP, tar)
      Oct 27: Cease-fire? - that's not my bag!
      Oct 28: Not exactly what he ordered!
      Oct 29: The agenda
      Oct 30: Quick - the cyclamates!
      Oct 31: Revised slogan
      Nov 3: The fledgling
      Nov 4: Still in the waiting room
      Nov 5: His baby now!
      Nov 6: How arrogant of him to think he's china!
      Nov 7: Why is Vietnamization so difficult? They did it up in north Vietnam years ago!
      Nov 10: Getting him out with honor (Vietnam, U.S.)
      Nov 11: Moral: never argue with a bulldozer
      Nov 12: Company's coming!
      Nov 13: Continuing alliance for progress
      Nov 14: When shall we three meet again?
      Nov 17: Effete corps of impudent snobs!
      Nov 18: The long wait
      Nov 19: The way of the dictator
      Nov 21: The toast
      Nov 24: Shucks! - even a president is human
      Nov 25: Why not a shovel too?
      Nov 26: One giant step for mankind!
      Nov 27: Institutionalized war
      Nov 28: Sh-h-h-h!
      Dec 1: What did they expect?
      Dec 2: Ah-ha! - now I see the enemy!
      Dec 3: That'll be the day
      Dec 4: Self-determination
      Dec 5: The gift list
      Dec 8: Lower your voice!
      Dec 9: U.S.A. - 1969
      Dec 10: Now do you want to be on Santa's good-boys list?
      Dec 11: Determining the dosage
      Dec 12: Boy - I've had it! Give me one ticket one way!
      Dec 15: Violence in the streets
      Dec 16: You'll have to wait - I'm busy with one over here!
      Dec 17: And there's another little problem
      Dec 18: Here's another one!
      Dec 19: Of course it's a long shot, but - !
      Dec 22: 'Tis the season to be jolly
      Dec 23: 'Tis the season!
      Dec 24: Anybody want a Christmas gift?
      Dec 26: Pity the poor!
      Dec 29: How many more mileposts?
      Dec 30: 1970? - I hardly know where we've been in 1969!
    - 1970 Jan-Apr (Oversize 51)
      Jan 2: Not a very apt pupil!
      Jan 5: It's the indignity of it!
      Jan 6: Letter from the earthlings
      Jan 7: Split in the silent majority?
      Jan 8: The white man's burden
      Jan 9: Poverty in the cities
      Jan 12: Any time is seeding-time!
      Jan 13: Uneven match
      Jan 14: How to bring us together!
      Jan 15: Still the guiding light
      Jan 16: Man of the century!
      Jan 19: They say the blossoms are beautiful!
      Jan 20: Bringing them together!
      Jan 21: At least we're getting some action!
      Jan 22: Why do I always get the left-overs?
      Jan 23: Futuristic painter (Nixon, state of the union)
      Jan 26: Too many priorities!
      Jan 27: What do you mean - recession?
      Jan 28: The heat is on!
      Jan 29: Inflation, ya know!
      Jan 30: Yes, it's a nasty war!
      Feb 2: No recession here!
      Feb 3: What did he expect?
      Feb 4: On the hook!
      Feb 5: The fireman
      Feb 6: Don't go 'way - I may call on you after all (U.S. world cop, Nixon)
      Feb 9: How about a hedge against inflation?
      Feb 10: Dr. Laird calling
      Feb 11: Hey - that's my garbage can!
      Feb 12: Two little black boxes
      Feb 13: Dangerous poker game (Soviet arms, U.S. arms, Mideast)
      Feb 16: I ain't goin' to budge!
      Feb 17: Big Brother comes in many forms (censorship)
      Feb 19: The message
      Feb 20: Laos? - I thought it was Vietnam!
      Feb 23: Why doncha go out and get a job?
      Feb 25: (no caption)
      Feb 26: Let's toast the past - there is no future (USSR military, USA military, ABM)
      Feb 27: And the secret is coming out (Nixon, American people, Cambodia, Laos, Thailand)
      Mar 3: Defying the law of gravity
      Mar 4: What's the matter with everybody?
      Mar 5: Has he lost his way?
      Mar 6: A ray of hope
      Mar 9: There's gotta be a rabbit!
      Mar 10: If we're really serious about pollution control!
      Mar 11: The handicap
      Mar 12: The ultimate weapon!
      Mar 13: Here comes the life preserver!
      Mar 16: What do kids know about politics?
      Mar 17: Long road to where? (Vietnamization)
      Mar 18: Man and his world
      Mar 19: Economic teeter-totter
      Mar 20: Whose side are you on?!
      Mar 23: (no caption)
      Mar 24: What happened?
      Mar 25: There'll be a slight delay!
      Mar 26: Bring back the mail strike!
      Mar 27: It's a big market!
      Mar 30: Sort of an endurance test
      Mar 31: Now tell me about your dreams!
      Apr 1: Is this the only way to fly the flag
      Apr 2: Trying to save his honor!
      Apr 3: Political campaign slogan?
      Apr 6: Hypnotized?
      Apr 7: What's the world coming to?!
      Apr 8: What's the hurry?
      Apr 9: Bull market
      Apr 10: Wrong road
      Apr 13: Slow learner
      Apr 14: Now keep your eye on the ball!
      Apr 15: Bringing them together (USA, USSR, atomic horror)
      Apr 16: More seasoning than stew!
      Apr 17: By golly, we got Earl Warren (Bill Douglas)
      Apr 20: - and what is the lesson for today?
      Apr 21: What's so bad about pollution when it's for a good cause? (god of war)
      Apr 22: Advanced course
      Apr 23: Another invitation!
      Apr 24: Famous last words
      Apr 27: We need another bucket of sand!.
      Apr 28: Fancy meeting you here!
      Apr 29: I thought we were getting out (Cambodia etc., U.S., the military)
      Apr 30: Wall street tango
    - 1970 Jan-Apr (Oversize 51)
      Jan 1: Go back!
      Jan 5: Why doesn't kitty come down?
      Jan 6: This isn't really sacred after all!
      Jan 7: Ten years of a floundering giant (Indochina, U.S.)
      Jan 8: Perilous pollution
      Jan 11: I thought you'd gone!
      Jan 12: Nice form - now keep rowing!
      Jan 13: The early birds
      Jan 14: The money game
      Jan 15: My poor little world - I may have to destroy you to save you!
      Jan 18: The defendant
      Jan 19: Revolving doors are wonderful!
      Jan 20: The game plan that failed!
      Jan 21: His own state of the union address!
      Jan 22: A matter of priorities
      Jan 25: I told you we were getting out of Vietnam!
      Jan 26: Here - unscramble these eggs and• come up with something better!
      Jan 27: - and his shadow!
      Jan 28: From the mountaintop!
      Jan 29: What kind of behavior is this?
      Feb 1: Military strategy simplified
      Feb 4: The new congress
      Feb 5: Revenue sharing with a bang!
      Feb 8: - and, Alan, if you boys should see any gold nuggets up there...
      Feb 9: Demonstrating the domino theory!
      Feb 10: What a long nose you have, uncle!
      Feb 11: Who'll administer this - Washington or the states?
      Feb 12: Pity the poor ecologist!
      Feb 15: One small step for mankind!
      Feb 16: And now our domestic problems!
      Feb 17: The boy at the dike
      Feb 18: Revenue sharing is old stuff!
      Feb 19: Full dress for withdrawal?
      Feb 23: Doncha want to be big and strong?
      Feb 24: Why, there goes the parson (GOP deficit spending)
      Feb 25: Advanced studies
      Feb 26: Maybe you could be a little more subtle!
      Mar 1: Global drug addiction
      Mar 2: Latest bulletin
      Mar 3: Juggernaut
      Mar 4: Another Indochina action shaping up!
      Mar 5: The great coat of Minnesota
      Mar 8: Counting his chickens
      Mar 9: Most fun I've had in years!
      Mar 10: Getting ideas!
      Mar 11: Thank you, Mr. President!
      Mar 12: But I'm not a racist!
      Mar 15: Hey, doc, take me back - this is not for me!
      Mar 16: Investigating himself
      Mar 17: Uncle! - don't you recognize me?
      Mar 19: The pause
      Mar 22: Now the responsibility gap!
      Mar 23: Crossing swords (USSR, China)
      Mar 24: Maybe I'm losing my charisma!
      Mar 25: More than a sonic boom!
      Mar 26: Record of achievement
      Mar 29: Maybe we ought to do something!
      Mar 30: Kid, you're lookin' great!
      Mar 31: Somebody has to pay for it!
      Apr 1: Out, damned spot!
      Apr 2: This is an outrage!
      Apr 5: Will it come to this?
      Apr 6: Paper work
      Apr 7: Thanks, judge!
      Apr 8: Pity the poor pedestrian!
      Apr 9: I'm staking my political future on you - now don't let me down!
      Apr 12: That inscrutable oriental!
      Apr 13: Better than missiles!
      Apr 15: Of course in our role we can't get completely out!
      Apr 16: Haven't we met before someplace?
      Apr 19: Warning!
      Apr 20: This is my number one priority!
      Apr 21: I feel quite cozy here!
      Apr 22: Not our finest hour!
      Apr 23: Why can't we let the next generation do it?
      Apr 26: Still another spring
      Apr 27: This is what made America great!
      Apr 28: Some sort of recognition!
      Apr 29: Lighting the way to a police state
      Apr 30: On trial
    - 1971 Sep-1972 Feb (Oversize 52)
      Sep 1: Ladie-e-e-es and gentlemen...!
      Sep 2: Back to school
      Sep 3: Not enough pie - or too many knives?
      Sep 6: Victory in Vietnam (Thieu, U.S., self-determination doctrine)
      Sep 7: Charge!
      Sep 8: The killing goes on!
      Sep 9: The freeze is old stuff for him!
      Sep 10: Global questions
      Sep 13: Automation
      Oct 5: World champion shadowboxer!
      Oct 6: Throwback?
      Oct 7: Homework
      Oct 8: If you guys want my services, you've got to help pay for it!
      Oct 11: Recalling the good old days!
      Oct 12: There ain't no such animal!
      Oct 13: Breath-taking!
      Oct 14: I like this one-way idea!
      Oct 15: Now I expect you fellows to show some self-control!
      Oct 18: Speaking of casualties (Indochina)
      Oct 20: Getting a feel for it
      Oct 21: Another one-man election!
      Oct 22: Phase two?
      Oct 25: Reconnoitering
      Oct 26: How many times has that been recycled?
      Oct 27: So you're china - welcome to the club!
      Oct 28: Tough going for the buses!
      Oct 29: 20th century jousting
      Nov 1: He has his phases, too!
      Nov 2: Someone will have to rescue the baby!
      Nov 3: Well, I got her off dead center! (global politics)
      Nov 4: I may have to destroy it to save it!
      Nov 5: The troika
      Nov 8: (no caption)
      Nov 9: I'm going to kick this habit someday!
      Nov 10: The bugs will get you if the chemicals don't!
      Nov 11: Breaking home ties
      Nov 12: But where will he go? (isolationism)
      Nov 15: The takeoff
      Nov 16: Louder, please!
      Nov 17: Floating
      Nov 18: I say, walls make good neighbors!
      Nov 19: Buddy, can you spare a million?
      Nov 22: Now, what phase is this?
      Nov 23: Of course, some inflation is 0.k.!
      Nov 24: But there's money there!
      Nov 25: Are these the helping hands?
      Nov 26: Same old phase for him!
      Nov 29: Prime defensive stock
      Nov 30: Geography lesson
      Dec 1: Are you really mad?!
      Dec 2: All it takes is a little patience°
      Dec 3: Isn't that old moneybags, himself?
      Dec 6: Another farm problem!
      Dec 8: Speaking of banning unsafe toys (jingoists, super-patriots, nuclear weapons)
      Dec 9: Want ad
      Dec 10: Putting on the brakes
      Dec 13: The boy on the burning deck
      Dec 14: No riders!
      Dec 17: Landing problems
      Dec 20: The. Stocking is still hanging
      Dec 21: Talk about crime in the streets!
      Dec 22: For some the war is winding down
      Dec 23: He's got the ball - or has he?
      Dec 24: Goulash
      Dec 27: Where's the exchange department?
      Dec 28: Coo-coo-oooo!
      Dec 30: Which way are the winds blowing?
      1972
      Jan 3: Annual generation gap (1972)
      Jan 4: Inveterate optimist
      Jan 5: The growing specter
      Jan 6: Still sitting on it!
      Jan 7: Exciting foreign policy drama
      Jan 10: Into the 11th year of frustration!
      Jan 11: No cutback in this rocketry!
      Jan 12: There's bound to be a leak!
      Jan 13: Slight odds on the elephant!
      Jan 14: Not on the president's itinerary!
      Jan 17: Living it up (world's resources)
      Jan 18: State of the union message
      Jan 19: Back to work with gusto!
      Jan 20: Lively corpse!
      Jan 21: Where there is always sunshine!
      Jan 24: It's all academic to me!
      Jan 25: Battle of the red ink!
      Jan 26: Sort of bullish!
      Jan 27: (no caption)
      Jan 28: Russian roulette
      Jan 31: Secret weapon?
      Feb 1: Still America's darling
      Feb 2: At the end of the rainbow
      Feb 3: Another population explosion!
      Feb 7: Humpty dumpty
      Feb 8: Another amnesty candidate!
      Feb 9: Of course, this is only my own personal point of view!
      Feb 10: Pres. Nixon: great step toward peace
      Feb 11: Winding down the war!
      Feb 14: But I still have my honor (Southeast Asia, colonialism)
      Feb 15: Hear no evil!
      Feb 16: Missiles to the east of us - missiles to the west of us!
      Feb 17: The stay-at-home
      Feb 18: Not exactly a thriller!
      Feb 21: See - it really isn't very big!
      Feb 22: Summit preliminaries
      Feb 23: Traitor!
      Feb 24: Purr-r-r-r
      Feb 25: I suppose his defection to china would be too good to hope for!
      Feb 28: It's a political year!
      Feb 29: The week that changed the world!
    - 1972 Mar-Aug (Oversize 53)
      Mar 1: Try to digest that while I prepare for another trip!
      Mar 2: Find the one with the earplugs
      Mar 3: Disengagement posture
      Mar 6: The morning after
      Mar 7: The affluent society (political campaigning)
      Mar 8: Needed: new wonder drug!
      Mar 9: V is for violence!
      Mar 10: Now, what did you say?
      Mar 13: Kind of gives you a sense of balance!
      Mar 14: Gosh! - how can I afford it?
      Mar 15: The real driver
      Mar 16: Here are some more stabilizers!
      Mar 17: Qualifying for the presidency?
      Mar 20: Still hot!
      Mar 21: Playing chicken
      Mar 22: In the land of the free?
      Mar 23: I suppose it is a lot of fun!
      Mar 24: More crocodile tears!
      Mar 27: Election of a president
      Mar 28: Some day there'll be a forced landing!
      Mar 29: I never liked back-seat drivers!
      Mar 30: The ITT hot line!
      Mar 31: The long march!
      Apr 3: The new protester
      Apr 4: Gosh! - I thought you had gone!
      Apr 5: Spring has arrived on the city parkways!
      Apr 6: The carpetbagger
      Apr 7: What are the primary winds saying?
      Apr 10: I thought this was nesting time!
      Apr 11: Elections now going on in Vietnam!
      Apr 12: The presidential open
      Apr 13: How it must feel at first!
      Apr 14: The shattering burst of-a bubble!
      Apr 18: Some people just don't understand!
      Apr 19: Serpentine fuse
      Apr 20: Invasion on the home front!
      Apr 21: Era of the strategist
      Apr 24: Watching George do it!
      Apr 25: Eyeball to eyeball!
      Apr 26: Because it's there!
      Apr 27: Even bigger than it looks!
      Apr 28: The urgent summit
      May 1: I hope I won't have to destroy it to save it!
      May 2: Don't you understand? - my security depends on you!
      May 3: The road to Moscow
      May 4: Put it back together and you still have Vietnamization!
      May 5: Help!
      May 8: Western civilization has brought us a lot of wonderful gadgets!
      May 9: Horse fly!
      May 10: Did I hear a bugle?
      May 11: Environmental bill collector
      May 12: Sailor, beware!
      May 15: Uncomfortable platform
      May 16: Marking the ballot
      May 17: What makes civilians so violent?!
      May 18: I do like this uniform!
      May 19: You back again?
      May 22: Well, pat - this is it!
      May 23: Convention drummer
      May 24: The big three (USA, USSR, Vietnam)
      May 25: Old politics - new technology
      May 29: It's a start, anyway!
      May 30: Is it real or is it a hoax?
      May 31: This deprives me of my rights!
      Jun 1: Political popularity chart?
      Jun 2: Strange way to train for the championship!
      Jun 5: Can everybody hear me?
      Jun 6: The era of. Summits?
      Jun 7: This has been so successful -
      Jun 9: I think I smell smoke!
      Jun 12: Has anyone seen a smart dove?
      Jun 13: Idealism, limited
      Jun 20: Another endangered species!
      Jun 21: You, too?!
      Jun 22: Coming in for a landing
      Jun 23: Ever see such a mad hare?
      Jun 27: Pops, why can't we work this out together?
      Jun 28: Guess who's the top man!
      Jun 29: The grim race
      Jun 30: Thou shalt not kill!
      Jul 3: Mounting the platform!
      Jul 4: Not so fast, mister (ecology, business as usual)
      Jul 5: It's music to one pair of ears!
      Jul 6: Shucks, the world chess championship is old stuff!
      Jul 7: Wonder what he has in his bags!
      Jul 10: The convention will now come to order!
      Jul 11: Doomsday is just around the corner!
      Jul 12: Still wearing the crown!
      Jul 13: See how fortunate you are!
      Jul 14: To the victor!